Might be hard for you to hear in your life,
you will inevitably misspeak.
Trust the wrong person.
Underreact, overreact. Hurt the
people who didn't deserve it. Overthink.
Not think at all. Self sabotage.
Create a reality where only your experience exists.
Ruin perfectly good moments for yourself and others. Deny any
wrongdoing not take the steps to make it right. Feel very guilty.
Let the guilt eat at you. Hit rock bottom.
Finally, address the pain you caused. Try to do better next
time. Rinse, repeat. And I'm not going to lie,
these mistakes will cause you to lose things.
I'm trying to tell you that losing things doesn't
just mean losing. A lot of the time. When we lose
things, we gain things too.