Might be hard for you to hear in your
life, you will inevitably misspeak.
Trust the wrong person.
Underreact, overreact. Hurt the people
who didn't deserve it. Overthink.
Not think at all. Self sabotage.
Create a reality where only your experience exists.
Ruin perfectly good moments for yourself and others. Deny any
wrongdoing not take the steps to make it right. Feel very
guilty. Let the guilt eat at you. Hit rock
bottom. Finally, address the pain you caused. Try to
do better next time. Rinse, repeat.
And I'm not going to lie, these mistakes will
cause you to lose things. I'm trying to tell
you that losing things doesn't just
mean losing. A lot of the time.